<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HomeScreen</string>

    <string name="terms_and_conditions_label" >
        1. Introduction\n \n

        CIQ Web offers pre-trained computer vision (CV) capabilities to extract information and insights from images. This Feature utilizes machine learning and AI algorithms to analyze images uploaded by users. By using the image recognition feature ("Feature") provided by NineBit Computing Pvt. Ltd., you agree to abide by these Terms and Conditions.\n \n

2. User Responsibilities\n  \n

a. You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible for any images you upload and the results generated by the Feature.\n \n

b. You agree not to upload any images that are potentially unsafe, inappropriate, illegal, or violate the rights of any third party.\n \n

c. You understand and agree that the accuracy and reliability of the results generated by the Feature may vary and that we make no guarantees regarding the same.\n \n

3. Use of Results\n \n

a. Any results generated by the Feature are provided for informational purposes only and should not be relied upon as the sole basis for making decisions.\n \n

b. You agree that we shall not be liable for any damages or losses arising from your reliance on the results generated by the Feature.\n \n

4. Indemnification\n \n

You hereby indemnify and hold harmless NineBit Computing Pvt. Ltd. and its affiliates, officers, employees, agents, and licensors from and against any and all claims, liabilities, damages, losses, costs, expenses, or fees (including reasonable attorneys\' fees) arising from your use of the Feature or any violation of these Terms and Conditions.\n \n

5. Limitation of Liability\n \n

In no event shall we be liable to you or any third party for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages arising out of or in any way connected with your use of the Feature, whether based on warranty, contract, tort (including negligence), or any other legal theory, and whether or not we have been informed of the possibility of such damage.\n \n

6. Modification of Terms\n \n

We reserve the right to modify these Terms and Conditions at any time without prior notice. Your continued use of the Feature after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the new Terms and Conditions.\n \n

7. Governing Law &amp; Jurisdiction\n \n

These Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Court of Indore, M.P., and you agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in Indore, M.P. for the resolution of any disputes.\n \n

8. Entire Agreement\n \n

These Terms and Conditions, together with any other policies or agreements referenced herein, constitute the entire agreement between you and NineBit Computing Pvt. Ltd. regarding the Feature and supersede all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral, or written, between you and us.\n \n
</string>
    <string name="UploadFile_label">Upload files</string>

    <string name="dragDrop_label">Drag &amp; drop your files here</string>

    <string name="dragDrop_or_label">or</string>

    <string name="browseButton_label">Choose files from your device</string>

    <string name="preview_text_label">Preview</string>

    <string name="previewUpload_button_label">Upload</string>

    <string name="previewCancel_button_label">Cancel</string>

    <string name="dialog_box_label">Are you sure you want to cancel?</string>

    <string name="preview_success_label">Preview Successful</string>

</resources>


